const quiz = [
    {
        "category": "JavaScript",             // Category shown on category selection button
        "questions": [                        // Question set object can accommodate any number of categories and questions per category
            {                                 // Answer sets can be fewer than four answers, but more than four may exceed the UI limits for some viewports
                "question": "What is the command for printing to console?",                         // Correct answer in first position of every answer set
                "answers": ["console.log()", "output.log()", "toConsole()", "console.out()"]        // Answers are randomly shuffled when displayed
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these does not declare a variable?",
                "answers": ["num", "var", "let", "const"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these is not a primitive data type?",
                "answers": ["Value", "String", "Symbol", "Null"]
            },
            {
                "question": "How many possible values can booleans have?",
                "answers": ["Two", "One", "Three", "Unlimited"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which conditional requires equal value but not type?",
                "answers": ["x == y", "x === y", "x !== y", "x = y"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these in a conditional statement signify 'or'?",
                "answers": ["||", "&&", "or", "><"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these signifies 'if x is not true'?",
                "answers": ["if (!x)", "else if (x)", "if (x !== false)", "if !(x = true)"]
            },
            {
                "question": "At which index is x in the array [a, b, x, y]?",
                "answers": ["2", "1", "3", "4"]
            },
            {
                "question": "How many cycles are in this loop? for(var i = 0; i < 3; i++)",
                "answers": ["Three", "Four", "Two", "Infinite"]
            },
            {
                "question": "What will array.pop() remove from an array?",
                "answers": ["Last element", "First element", "All elements", "Nothing"]
            },
            {
                "question": "How many properties can an object have?",
                "answers": ["Unlimited", "Zero", "Up to ten", "One"]
            },
            {
                "question": "What must be given to satisfy a function's parameters?",
                "answers": ["Arguments", "Local variables", "Conditions", "Indices"]
            }
        ]
    }
    ,
    {
        "category": "Marvel",
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "In the Days of Future Past comic book run, who is sent to the past?",
                "answers": ["Kitty Pryde", "Wolverine", "Professor X", "Bishop"]
            },
            {
                "question": "What is Ororo Munroe's mutant power?",
                "answers": ["Weather", "Teleportation", "Telepathy", "Voodoo"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which newspaper does J. Jonah Jameson work for?",
                "answers": ["The Daily Bugle", "The Daily Planet", "The New Yorker", "The New York Herald"]
            },
            {
                "question": "What planet is Drax the Destroyer from?",
                "answers": ["Earth", "Titan", "Xandar", "Saturn"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Namor is the ruler of which realm?",
                "answers": ["Atlantis", "Wakanda", "Krakoa", "Asgard"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which power source does Jean Grey have access to?",
                "answers": ["The Phoenix Force", "The Power Cosmic", "Chaos Magic", "Negative Energy"]
            },
            {
                "question": "In which Realm was Loki born?",
                "answers": ["Jotunheim", "Asgard", "Nidavellir", "Alfheim"]
            },
            {
                "question": "How did the Fantastic Four get their powers?",
                "answers": ["Cosmic rays", "Gamma ray burst", "Mutation", "A curse"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of The Watchers primarily observes Earth-616?",
                "answers": ["Uatu", "Ubuntu", "Umar", "Ultimo"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these characters is the sister of Captain Britain?",
                "answers": ["Psylocke", "Agatha Harkness", "Wanda Maximoff", "Pepper Potts"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Captain America was the product of which program?",
                "answers": ["Project: Rebirth", "Weapon X", "Winter Soldier", "Avengers"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Whose brainwaves were used to create The Vision?",
                "answers": ["Wonder Man", "Iron Man", "Hulk", "Hawkweye"]
            }
        ]
    }
]